in this and the next lecture I will
在这节课和下一节课中，我将
integrate a graph with an image to start
将图形与图像整合以开始
let's import the sketch I have for the
让我们将我的草图导入到
end result I go to file import and open
最终结果我去文件导入并打开
the sketch I hold shift plus control and
我按住Shift+Ctrl的素描
make the sketch a bit smaller I call the
把素描做小一点，我称之为
image sketch and lock it I set the
图像素描并锁定它我设置了
opacity to 25 and the blend mode to
不透明度设置为25，混合模式设置为
multiply I create a new layer and call
乘以我创建一个新层并调用
it legs now I import the image of the
它的腿现在我导入的形象
soccer player I call the image bicycle
足球运动员我称其为自行车形象
kick I will increase the size of the
Kick I将增加大小
image until it roughly fits the sketch
图像，直到它与素描大致相符
outline as we see with the end result I
正如我们在最终结果中看到的那样，大纲是
need the legs to be cut out
我需要把腿切掉
normally you don't need the high
正常情况下，你不需要兴奋
Precision like the letter we traced in
就像我们追踪到的字母一样精确
the last lecture the node tool in
上一课中的节点工具
inkscape lets you trace an image
Inkscape允许您跟踪图像
extremely fast and the node tool offers
速度极快，节点工具提供
many possibilities to customize the
有多种可能来自定义
result when needed I will hide the
结果在需要时，我会隐藏
sketch before we can utilize the node
在我们可以使用该节点之前，请先绘制草图
tool I will first place some nodes
工具，我将首先放置一些节点
around the legs using the pen tool
使用钢笔工具围绕腿部
I will place points by roughly following
我将通过大致如下的方式来放置点数
the shape of the legs as we see I do not
我们看到的腿的形状我不知道
make any curves I just place a point
做任何曲线，我只需放置一个点
when there is a change in Direction I
当方向I发生变化时
don't worry about curves the node tool
不要担心节点工具中的曲线
is much faster at creating curves with
在创建曲线方面速度要快得多
the football I only click on the outer
足球我只点了一下外面
edges as we saw in the last lecture
就像我们在上一节课中看到的那样
so I only click at the bottom the left
所以我只点击底部的左边
and the top of the ball
和球的顶端
where there is some more important
那里有一些更重要的
detail I will zoom in a bit and place
细节我将放大一点并放置在
some points what is chopped off by the
一些点被砍掉了
straight lines will be corrected by the
直线将由
node tool
节点工具
so I click there where there are changes
所以我在有变化的地方点击
in the direction of the Curve also for
在曲线的方向上也是为了
the bottom of the shoe I click
我点了一下鞋底
pretending my lines are curved even
假装我的线条是弯曲的
though they are not even the sharp
尽管他们甚至不是最锋利的
points of the soccer shoe studs will be
足球鞋螺柱的分数将是
taken care of by the node tool when I
在我执行以下操作时由节点工具处理
have reached the shorts again I can
已经再次到达短裤，我可以
close the path to do this I click again
关闭路径以执行此操作我再次单击
on the first point
关于第一点
now I select the node tool I will select
现在，我选择要选择的节点工具
some nodes that I don't need by dragging
通过拖动不需要的一些节点
over them then I press delete now I will
在它们上面，然后我现在按删除，我会
match the curves by simply dragging the
只需拖动
lines
线条
I wouldn't do this to trace letters but
我不会这么做来追踪信件，但是
it works extremely fast I have traced
据我所知，它的运行速度非常快
many images in and Photoshop in the
和Photoshop中的许多图像
past but the node tool of inkscape is
过去，Inkscape的节点工具是
probably my favorite tool to trace
可能是我最喜欢的追踪工具
images
图像
this way of working doesn't give the 100
这种工作方式不会给100
accuracy that for example is needed when
例如，在以下情况下需要的准确性
you create a logo
您可以创建一个徽标
but for tracing bitmap images in my
而是为了在我的
opinion this isn't needed to get good
观点认为这不是变好所必需的
results
结果
as we see I have full control over the
正如我们所见，我完全控制了
curve I drag a line and can get it any
曲线我拖着一条线，可以得到它的任何
curvature I want and if I want to add a
我想要的曲率，如果我想添加一个
point I simply double click on a line
点I只需双击一条线即可
so now let's look at some extra features
现在让我们来看看一些额外的功能
that the node tool provides I drew the
节点工具提供的，我绘制了
spikes of the bottom shoe with a single
鞋底的钉子上有一个单钉
note if I find this a bit too pointy I
注意，如果我觉得这个太尖了，我
can easily make them more round
可以很容易地让它们变得更圆
I select the spikes by shift clicking on
我通过按Shift键选择钉子
them then I click on the make selected
然后我点击Make Selected(选定)
node smooth icon
节点平滑图标
now let's have a look at the other foot
现在让我们来看看另一只脚
I will drag over the top nodes and
我会将鼠标拖到顶部节点上
smooth them it does give me the result I
抚平他们，它确实给了我结果，我
need but you can do more as we see with
需要，但您可以做更多，正如我们所看到的
a smooth note the arms are linked but
流畅的音符手臂是相连的，但
let's say I want to move the arms
假设我想移动手臂
independently to do this click once on
要独立完成此操作，请单击
the make selected nodes Corner icon
将选定节点设为角点图标
we see the node changed from a square to
我们看到节点从正方形变为
a diamond the arms are not connected
一颗钻石，两只手臂不相连
anymore
更多
and if you want to remove the arms click
如果您想移除手臂，请单击
on the make selected nodes Corner icon a
在将选定节点设置为角点图标上
second time
第二次
I will make the node smooth again if you
我会让节点再次变得光滑，如果你
want the arms of a node to have the same
希望节点的手臂具有相同的
length at all times click on make
任何时候都要长点击Make(制作)
selected nodes symmetric if I drag an
如果我将选定节点拖动到
arm I see the other arm is mirrored in
手臂我看到另一只手臂是镜面上的
the node Auto smooth gives special kind
节点自动平滑提供特殊类型
of arms that adjusts themselves when you
你的手臂会自动调整，当你
drag the note
拖动便笺
I will go back to a smooth node where
我会回到一个平稳的节点，在那里
the arms are linked but can have their
手臂是相连的，但可以有他们的
own length if you want to create a
如果您想要创建
straight line between two curved nodes
两个曲线节点之间的直线
select the nodes
选择节点
then click on straighten lines now the
然后点击拉直线，现在
path between the nodes is straight and
节点之间的路径是直的，并且
the nodes are locked in their Direction
节点在其方向上被锁定
this locking is to prevent the straight
这种锁定是为了防止直线
line to curve when you adjust the
当您调整
handles and to go back to a curve simply
控制柄并简单地返回到曲线
drag the line if you want to give an arm
如果你想伸出援手，就拖这条线
a different direction but you don't want
一个不同的方向，但你不想
to change the length of an arm hold the
要更改手臂的长度，请按住
ALT key
Alt键
and to add a point simply double-click
要添加一个点，只需双击
on a line as we see there are many ways
就像我们看到的那样，有很多种方式
to manipulate a curve with a node tool
使用节点工具操纵曲线
if you don't want to see the arms
如果你不想看到手臂
deselect the show bezier handles icon
取消选择显示Bezier句柄图标
and to hide the path itself deselect the
要隐藏路径本身，请取消选择
show path outline icon I will delete
显示我要删除的路径轮廓图标
some nodes
一些节点
to quickly add nodes without having to
快速添加节点，而无需
double-click many times select two nodes
多次双击选择两个节点
then click on insert new nodes into
然后单击将新节点插入到
selected segments each time you click
每次单击时选择的线段
the amount of added nodes will double
添加的节点数将增加一倍
now my path is ready let's use the path
现在我的路已经准备好了，我们走这条路吧
to cut out the legs I call the path legs
为了把腿剪掉，我把这条路叫做腿
I right click on the path and choose set
我在路径上单击鼠标右键并选择Set
clip group I drag the image on the clip
剪辑组我将图像拖动到剪辑上
group folder I want my image to be
组文件夹我希望我的图像是
duotone so I will add a blue rectangle I
双色调，所以我会添加一个蓝色矩形
click on a blue I call the rectangle
点击一个我称之为矩形的蓝色
blue I set blue to the color blend mode
蓝色我将颜色混合模式设置为蓝色
I click on fill and stroke I can now
我点击填充和描边，我现在可以
give the duotone the correct color I
给双色调配上正确的颜色
drag the blue a bit more to cyan
将蓝色再拖动一点到青色
in the next lecture we will place the
在下一节课中，我们将把
bars in the text
文本中的条形图